<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[AloNews]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[AloNews delivers up-to-the-minute news and information on the latest top stories, weather, entertainment, politics and more.]]></description>
        <link>http://github.com/dylang/node-rss</link>
        <generator>RSS for Node</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 12:42:15 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <copyright><![CDATA[All rights reserved 2023, AloNews]]></copyright>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[NBA playoffs: Golden State Warriors edge past the Sacramento Kings despite botched timeout to level series]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>The&nbsp;<a href="https://cnn.com/2023/04/19/sport/draymond-green-golden-state-warriors-suspension-spt/index.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Golden State Warriors</a>&nbsp;narrowly beat the&nbsp;<a href="https://cnn.com/2023/03/30/sport/sacramento-kings-nba-basketball-playoffs-spt-intl/index.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Sacramento Kings</a>&nbsp;in a playoff thriller, winning 126-125 to level the first round series at 2-2.</p><p>Former Warrior Harrison Barnes, who played a key role in Golden State’s 2015 title run, missed a game-winning buzzer beater that would have given&nbsp;<a href="https://cnn.com/2023/04/17/sport/e-40-sacramento-kings-warriors-ejection-spt-intl/index.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Sacramento</a>&nbsp;a commanding series lead.</p><p>Warriors star guard Stephen Curry will have been more relieved than most to see Barnes’ three-point effort rim out.</p><p>With Golden State up five with just 45 seconds remaining, Curry called for a timeout without realizing his team was out of them, resulting in a technical foul and possession being given back to the Kings.</p><p>Malik Monk made the free throw for the technical foul and then Sacramento star De’Aaron Fox, who has earned a reputation this year for big buckets at crucial moments, hit a three-pointer to narrow the gap to just one.</p><p>Curry then missed his next effort and gave Barnes the chance to win the game, but the 30-year-old’s shot was just long, sparking jubilant scenes inside the Chase Center.</p><p>“I ain’t gonna lie, I thought it was the smartest play in the world,” Curry said after the game, per the NBA. “When I grabbed the ball and turned around and saw the trap, realized there was no real outlets instead of turning it over, it’s kind of the heady play, but it turned out not to be.</p><p>“I looked over at the bench and everyone was shaking their head, so it was an unfortunate situation in that respect. Thankfully, we came away with the win but good learning lesson on how important all those details are.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://localhost:3000/news/sport/nba-playoffs-golden-state-warriors</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:3000/news/sport/nba-playoffs-golden-state-warriors</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://localhost:3000/uploads/1682360242056-230424092756-03-nba-042323-warriors-kings-curry.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Kriss Kyle’s latest stunt takes a skate park 2,000 feet above the ground]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>When BMX&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2022/10/25/sport/dan-mancina-blind-skateboarder-intl-spt/index.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">freestyler</a>&nbsp;Kriss Kyle was out on a walk with his&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/03/27/sport/dog-catches-baseball-spring-training-spt-intl/index.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">dogs</a>&nbsp;during the pandemic, he looked up to the sky and saw a giant playground of potential for another of his daring deeds.</p><p>The Scotsman has become well known for performing death-defying stunts and this one would be no different.</p><p>“I thought I’d use the downtime [of the pandemic] to think of what is next and what has no one done before,” explains the&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2022/10/14/sport/felix-baumgartner-red-bull-sky-dive-spt-intl/index.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Red Bull</a>&nbsp;athlete.</p><p>“I was actually out walking my dogs and remember just daydreaming looking out at the sky and I was like, ‘Oh my God, imagine just a floating skate park in the sky.’”</p><p>Despite how crazy it sounds, crazy is what Kyle does and the wheels were set in motion for his most incredible challenge yet – performing BMX tricks on a skatepark hovering 2,000 feet above the ground.</p><p>The idea took three years from its inception to become a reality and Kyle describes the process as being “a lot harder than what [he] could ever [have] expected.”</p><p>Kyle was to be fitted with a parachute which weighed 10% of his body weight and the 31-year-old had to think of new ways to prepare for his ride in the sky.</p><p>“I had to start working out with my weighted vest on, lifting weights, a lot of stuff that I would never, ever do, you know, stuff that I’m not used to.”</p><p>Laughing, Kyle adds: “With this one, I actually had to gain muscle and actually sort my legs out because they were like little sticks.”</p><p>To make matters worse, the bowl he was riding in was not stationary like it would have been on&nbsp;<em>terra firma</em>&nbsp;– the flying skate park was “swinging around, four feet at a time.”</p><p>It made for a challenging experience from start to finish and Kyle candidly touched on this.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://localhost:3000/news/sport/kriss-kyle-latest-stunt-takes-a-skate-park</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:3000/news/sport/kriss-kyle-latest-stunt-takes-a-skate-park</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://localhost:3000/uploads/1682359334260-230418123428-kriss-kyle-red-bull-video-tease-balloon.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sifan Hassan lays claim to being greatest female distance runner with thrilling London Marathon victory]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><br></p><p>Running is a simple sport, the art of putting one foot in front of the other faster than your other competitors. That’s precisely what Sifan Hassan did in the<a href="http://www.cnn.com/2023/04/21/sport/mo-farah-london-marathon-protests-spt-intl/index.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">&nbsp;London Marathon</a>&nbsp;on Sunday, though her stunning, chaotic victory in the women’s race was anything but straightforward.</p><p>“There were so many dramas,” Hassan told reporters after the race, “so many dramas – but it’s beautiful.”</p><p>A three-time Olympic medalist and two-time world champion on the track, the win in London, one of the world’s six marathon majors, is the latest addition to the Dutch athlete’s remarkable running CV.</p><p>Hassan spent much of her debut marathon wondering when she would drop out having stopped to stretch an injured hip just after the hour mark. She later said she had forgotten to tape up her leg before taking to the start line.</p><p>Incredibly, Hassan appeared to shake off the injury and even picked up her pace as she gained on the lead group.</p><p>She had made up the lost ground by the closing stages, narrowly avoiding further disaster when she swerved towards a motorbike to collect her bottle from a drinks station.</p><p>Apparently unshaken by the near miss, Hassan recovered and had enough energy to outsprint Ethiopia’s Alemu Megertu and Kenya’s Peres Jepchirchir, the Olympic marathon champion, in the shadow of Buckingham Palace, breaking the finish tape in two hours, 18 minutes, and 34 seconds.</p><p>Not many athletes are able to replicate their success on the track over the 26.2 miles of the marathon, let alone at the first time of asking.</p><p>But Hassan, who won 5,000 and 10,000-meter golds at the Tokyo Olympics and a bronze in the 1,500 meters, is no ordinary athlete, such is her talent over a range of distances. She later downplayed the suggestion that she is the greatest female distance runner of all time.</p><p>“I’m not the greatest, I’m just okay,” the 30-year-old said. “I don’t need to become the greatest. I’m fine the way I am.”</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://localhost:3000/news/sport/sifan-hassan-lays-claim-to-being-greatest-female-distance-runner</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:3000/news/sport/sifan-hassan-lays-claim-to-being-greatest-female-distance-runner</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://localhost:3000/uploads/1682358825522-230424111422-01-sifan-hassan-london-marathon-042323.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Fox News, Tucker Carlson part ways days after Fox settles Dominion lawsuit]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>It was, above anything else, an editorial imperative. The right thing to do for our readers.</p><p>As The Atlantic’s deputy executive editor Sarah Yager puts it, making journalism is really about creating a record of the world around us. It’s about documenting what is happening and hopefully helping readers to make sense of it. And there’s enormous value in being able to learn from what was happening in the past, and how history was interpreted in real time.</p><p>The Atlantic had wanted to digitize its archive ever since it started publishing online in 1995. At that moment, a website for our magazine introduced the new opportunity for people to read the journalism we were writing that day, online. Our magazine, however, had been continuously printed and published since the autumn of 1857. There were a lot of stories that our readers couldn’t access online. From time to time editors would manually reproduce archival articles, but the massive task of making the archive available remained elusive for almost three decades.</p><p>How does one take tens of thousands of words from our print pages and publish them on the internet? How would The Atlantic suddenly go from not offering this content to having it on its data structure, its website presence? What are the mechanical steps to getting there? These were some of the questions that our product and technology colleagues asked themselves in May 2021, when the magazine committed to the challenge of bringing the archive online.</p><p>Hospitals in the country – which are short of blood supplies and life-saving equipment – are being targeted with military strikes by both the Army and the RSF, according to eyewitness accounts to CNN and two doctors’ organizations, leaving medical personnel unable to reach the wounded and to bury the dead.</p><p>One doctor at a Khartoum hospital – whom CNN is not naming for security reasons – said his facility has been targeted since Saturday. “A direct strike hit the maternity ward. We could hear heavy weaponry and lay on the floor, along with our patients. The hospital itself was under attack.”</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://localhost:3000/news/sport/fox-news-tucker-carlson</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:3000/news/sport/fox-news-tucker-carlson</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://localhost:3000/uploads/1682357978128-image 9.png" length="0" type="image/png"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Drew Maggi: Career minor leaguer finally gets MLB call-up after 13-year wait]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>They say good things come to those who wait, and Drew Maggi has been waiting a long time for his&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/04/20/sport/max-scherzer-ejected-substance-mets-dodgers-spt-intl/index.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">major league</a>&nbsp;call-up.</p><p>The third baseman for the Altoona Curve – the Pittsburgh Pirates’ AAA affiliate – was drafted by the Pirates in the 15th round of the 2010&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/04/23/sport/adolis-garcia-three-home-runs-rangers-athletics-spt-intl/index.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">MLB</a>&nbsp;draft but never played a&nbsp;<a href="https://www.cnn.com/2023/04/20/sport/oakland-athletics-las-vegas-move-mlb-spt-intl/index.html" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">big league</a>&nbsp;game.</p><p>The 33-year-old then went on a tour of various AAA and AA teams across the US before eventually returning to Pittsburgh in 2022 and re-signing in 2023.</p><p>Understandably, Maggi was pumped after spending his entire 13-year career in the minor leagues and celebrated alongside his teammates upon receiving the news.</p><p>Speaking to&nbsp;<a href="https://www.mlb.com/news/drew-maggi-added-to-pirates-big-league-roster" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">MLB.com</a>, Maggi touched on the emotions behind the call-up.</p><p>“This is where it all started for me. This whole year has been a big flashback of my younger self. I’m really happy with how it all turned out,” said Maggi.</p><p>“I know that 13 years is really hard. There were a lot of ups and downs, a lot of different people, injuries, a lot of stuff happens. You never know when your days are numbered. So, being here, it feels right.”</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://localhost:3000/news/sport/drew-maggi-career-minor-leaguer-finally-gets-mlb</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:3000/news/sport/drew-maggi-career-minor-leaguer-finally-gets-mlb</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://localhost:3000null" length="0" type="false"/>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Radio DJ Adele Roberts breaks record for fastest woman with an ileostomy to run the London Marathon]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>British radio presenter&nbsp;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CrYsdEzIMV8/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Adele Roberts&nbsp;</a>became the fastest woman to complete the London Marathon with an ileostomy, running the distance in just over three and a half hours on Sunday.</p><p>The&nbsp;<a href="https://twitter.com/GWR/status/1650165144935182336" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Guinness World Records&nbsp;</a>awarded Roberts with a framed certificate at the finish line, writing on Twitter: “Adele Roberts completed the fastest marathon with an ileostomy (female) in 3:30:22. Congratulations, Adele!”</p><p>Roberts, who is known for working on BBC Radio 1 in the UK, was&nbsp;<a href="https://twitter.com/AdeleRoberts/status/1452337685629128709" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">diagnosed</a>&nbsp;with bowel cancer in 2021 and began using a stoma bag after undergoing surgery 18 months ago.</p><p>The 44-year-old only stopped chemotherapy less than 12 months ago but recovered in time to set a new record.</p><p>“Thank you to every single person who has helped make today possible,” Roberts wrote on&nbsp;<a href="https://www.instagram.com/p/CrYsdEzIMV8/" rel="noopener noreferrer" target="_blank">Instagram</a>&nbsp;after the race.</p><p>“For those warriors living with cancer, for all the incredible ostomates around the UK and for the heroes of the NHS. That was for you.”</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://localhost:3000/news/sport/radio-dj-adele-roberts-breaks-records</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">http://localhost:3000/news/sport/radio-dj-adele-roberts-breaks-records</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 24 Apr 2023 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <enclosure url="http://localhost:3000/uploads/1682362505772-230424124458-adele-roberts-042323.jpg" length="0" type="image/jpeg"/>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>